Casey Morgan

715-651-4130

Wisconsin

caseyjeanmorgan@gmail.com

Profile

My name is Casey Morgan. I am 31 years old with a passion for change and growth, regardless of the field I am in. My training originates as a classical dancer and within these past 5 years I've really come to appreciate fitness, nutrition, and wellness. Today I am training as a Full-Stack Web Developer.

Experience

Sales Manager & Coach; Orangetheory fitness; Burnsville, MN 2018-present

I lead both Sales Associates and Coaches daily to keep the team in the know of the current sales, events, promotions, and knowledge of the brand. I handle administrative work to keep member accounts updated and I work closely with ownership to support the direction/vision of the brand. Some specific tasks include but are not limited to: Studio Culture and Vision; Staff Training- Systems and Processes; In Studio Events; Lead Management and Sales; Key Performance Indicators; Social Media and Marketing; Customer Service; Meetings; Staff Development and Reviews; Administrative responsibilities; Scheduling; Ensure Brand Policy Consistency; Retail Management.

Trainer; 4Ever Fit Studio; Rice Lake, WI; 2016-Present

I teach group fitness classes that focus on a variety of programming as well as fitness level. Predominantly, I am known as the Barre Fitness instructor at 4Ever Fit.

Dance instructor; Penni's Studio of the Arts; Bloomer, Wi; 2016-present

I teach all genres of dance and choreography to children 3-18 years of age.

Volunteer; Cameron High School dance team; cameron, wi; 2017-present

I help coach the dance team with my skills as a dancer and I help condition the team with my experience as a fitness instructor.

Dancer; West Virginia dance company; beckley, WV; 2014-2015

I performed educational shows for children K-12 traveling the state of West Virginia. Following our performance at these schools the dance company would hold a dance workshop that helped the children learn about the layers of the sun.

Dance/Gymnastics Instructor; YMCA; Mankato, MN; 2009-2011

I taught pre-schoolers the basic levels of dance and gymnastics. It was a very fun time to watch children grow to understand how their bodies function when attempting to move it in ways they've never moved before.

Education/Certifications/Training

Minnesota State University- Mankato Bachelor of Fine Arts; 2014

American Council on Exercise

Certified Group Fitness Instructor Expires 12/31/2021; Certification No. F122029

American Red Cross

Adult CPR/AED Standard First Aid Certified Expires 11/19/2020; Certificate ID: 14EKO1

National Exercise Trainers Association

Barre Connect Certification, 2/13/16 - 2/13/18

Skills

Communication, Ability to Work Under Pressure, Decision Making, Time Management, Self-motivation, Conflict Resolution, Leadership, Adaptability.

HTML; CSS; Bootstrap; Javascript; APOs; Node; ES6; Constructors; Classes; Objects; Inheritance; SQL; MySQL